http://www.gryphon-audio.dk/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentProductsPower AmplifiersPreamplifiersIntegrated AmplifiersCD PlayersPhonostagesLoudspeakersCablesD/A ConvertersAccessoriesFurnituresThe Gryphon StoryDistributors & DealersMoreCatalogueMerchandiseFor distributors & pressUsers CornerTechnicalFAQContactPrivacy PolicyGryphon Audio Designs Privacy Policy  Gryphon Audio Designs is committed to protecting the privacy of our website visitors, customers, distributors, and end users. We will be clear about the data we collect and why we are collecting it. We protect your data and will not misuse it or sell it to third parties. We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site.The purpose of this privacy policy statement is to explain the type of information Gryphon Audio Designs collects, either directly or indirectly, how we collect it, what we use it for and how users can restrict the use or disclosure of personally identifiable information collected.We confirm that we will keep your information secure and that we will comply fully with all applicable EU Data Protection legislation and regulations. INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE ITMost of our services on Gryphon Audio Designs website, do not require any form for registration, allowing you to visit the site without telling us who you are. However, for some specific services, we may require you to provide us with your personal data with direct identifiers (name, address etc.). Some of those specific services are optional and are up to the individual to fill out. GRYPHON CLUB – By filling our form and tick the section below the form, you agree to our Terms & Conditions and Privacy Policy. All your data registered in the form will purely be used for the purpose of sending Gryphon Club merchandise and information. CONTACT FORMULA – We request information from you on our order form. By filling the form you agree that we use your contact information in order to reply to your message.ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION – You may at any times contact us if you desire to change your personal information or want us to delete it from our archive.Contact the website administrator, Laura Patocska, for further information about the process. Email.: Laura@gryphon-audio.dk HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION? We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information.We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.DO WE USE COOKIES? Yes we use cookies. They are used so that we can provide a better service.LINKS This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information. Gryphon Audio Designs ApS Contact Information: DenmarkTel: +45 86891200CVR nr. DK 87296415
Go to Top
We use cookies to provide you the best possible experience. By using our site, you accept the use of cookies. Accept
